[{
        "question": "What is 1/2 + 1/4?",
        "answer": "3/4",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 2/3 - 1/6?",
        "answer": "1/2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 3/5 * 2/3?",
        "answer": "6/15",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 4/5 ÷ 2/3?",
        "answer": "6/5",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 2/7 + 4/7?",
        "answer": "6/7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 5/6 - 1/3?",
        "answer": "1/2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 3/8 * 4/9?",
        "answer": "1/6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 7/9 ÷ 3/4?",
        "answer": "28/27",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 1/3 + 2/5?",
        "answer": "11/15",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 3/4 - 1/8?",
        "answer": "5/8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 2/3 * 3/4?",
        "answer": "1/2",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 5/8 ÷ 3/4?",
        "answer": "10/12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 7/8 + 5/8?",
        "answer": "12/8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 4/9 - 2/9?",
        "answer": "2/9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 3/7 * 5/6?",
        "answer": "15/42",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 6/7 ÷ 2/3?",
        "answer": "9/7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {

        "question": "What is 5/12 + 1/4?",
        "answer": "8/12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 8/15 - 1/5?",
        "answer": "7/15",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 3/4 * 2/7?",
        "answer": "6/28",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is 5/6 ÷ 1/3?",
        "answer": "15/6",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]